MARK J. LINDSKOG

COLUMBUS, OH 43204 <u>lindskogmarkj@gmail.com</u> • (567) 203-9473 <u>LinkedIn</u> • <u>Github</u> • <u>Portfolio</u>

SUMMARY

Coding Bootcamp graduate with additional experience in software testing and Agile development, working in solo and team roles in web development projects. Developed strong communication and multitasking skills due to previous positions held in sales and marketing.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Javascript ES6+, CSS3, HTML5, SQL, NoSQL

Applications: GitHub, MongoDB, MySQL, Heroku, TestRail, Jira, Insomnia, Postman

Tools: Express, Node, Query, Handlebars, React, Bootstrap, Foundation, MUI, Charles Proxy

PROJECTS

Scriber | https://github.com/mjlindskog/scriber | https://powerful-shore-38656.herokuapp.com/

Summary: App for writers and note takers with text to speech functionality

Role: Front end author, text-to-speech implementer

Tools: Express, Node, JavaScript, MUI, React, Apollo GraphQL

EXPERIENCE

MoneyPigeon, Columbus, OH | July 2022 - Present

SOFTWARE QA ENGINEER

- Reviewing user interfaces for conformity and functionality by applying QA tools and methodologies
- Designing test cases in TestRail and providing test execution based on analysis of business requirements and specifications
- Configuring virtual devices applying BrowserStack, Android Studio and Xcode
- Identifying and reporting issues in Jira and monitoring defect status
- Designing data validation through a database with SQL-queries
- Performing API testing, creating collections and running different calls using Postman
- Collaborating with product manager and developers to meet the requirement and ensure a quality product

NuGrowth Solutions, Columbus, OH | February 2020 - May 2021

DEDICATED TACTIC GROUP CAMPAIGN REPRESENTATIVE

- Representative for multiple accounts in the market daily, tripling number of impressions in the market
- Create interest and generate pipeline development within a 90-day client cycle for each account

INSIDE SALES EXECUTIVE

- Contact to closure representative for UCaaS/Webinar platform provider (Onstream Media)
- Create over 250 impressions into the market each week through phone and email
- Product expert responsible for qualifying prospects and running through demonstrations

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Project Management Institute | Disciplined Agile and Scrum Master | 2022

Ohio State University | Coding Web Development Certificate | 2021

Ohio University - Athens, OH | Bachelor of Arts - History | 2015 - 2019